Sometimes True Love Can Have More Than One Face.
Serendipity is a comedy, romance film directed by Peter Chelsom.
Although strangers Sara and Jonathan are both already in relationships, they realize they
have genuine chemistry after a chance encounter – but part company soon after.
Years later, they each yearn to reunite, despite being destined for the altar.
But to give true love a chance, they have to find one another again.
Jonathan Trager, played by John Cusack.
Sara Thomas, played by Kate Beckinsale.
Dean Kansky, played by Jeremy Piven.
Halley Buchanan, played by Bridget Moynahan.
Lars Hammond, played by John Corbett.
Eve, played by Molly Shannon.
Serendipity is a 2001 American romantic comedy film directed by Peter Chelsom,
written by Marc Klein, and starring John Cusack and Kate Beckinsale.
The film grossed $77.5 million on a $28 million budget.
The film explores themes of new york city, new love,
soulmates, chance, love at first sight.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.